export default {
  video_question: [
    {
      question: "When do the Cups Disappear on the Lower #1’s?",
      answer: "6 Years Old"
    },
    {
      question: "Why does the tooth change shape as the Horse gets older?",
      answer: "The top of the tooth is rectangular, the middle is square, and the bottom is triangular. As the tooth wears, the surface reflects the portion of the tooth being used."
    },
    {
      question: "What composite backfills the Pulp Chamber as the Blood and Nerve Supply recede back into the Pulp Chamber?",
      answer: "Secondary Dentin"
    },
    {
      question: "When does the Dental Star appear on the Lower #2’s?",
      answer: "7 Years Old"
    },
    {
      question: "At what Age does the Galvayne’s Groove extend from the Gum line to Halfway down the Tooth?",
      answer: "15 Years Old"
    },
    {
      question: "When does a Horse shed their Upper #2 Caps (Babyteeth)?",
      answer: "3 1⁄2 Years Old"
    },
    {
      question: "When does all evidence of the Cup finally disappear from the Lower #3’s?",
      answer: "17 Years Old"
    },
    {
      question: "At what Age does the Galvayne’s Groove extend from the Halfway down the Tooth to all the way out the bottom?",
      answer: "25 Years Old"
    },
    {
      question: "Why does the Cup disappear on the Uppers #3 years later than it disappears on the Lowers if they are the exact same age?",
      answer: "The Upper Cup and Tooth are so much big than the Lower Cup and Tooth."
    },
    {
      question: "What composite is the darkest material on the surface of the tooth?",
      answer: "Secondary Dentin"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the darkest material on the surface of the tooth known as in Aging?",
      answer: "The Dental Star"
    },
    {
      question: "When is the Cup considered worn on the Upper #3’s?",
      answer: "11 Years Old"
    },
    {
      question: "What Composite protects enamel on the Outside of the Tooth?",
      answer: "Cementum"
    },
    {
      question: "Do mares get Wolf Teeth?",
      answer: "Yes"
    },
    {
      question: "What years do the “Vegas” or Upper #3 Hooks Appear?",
      answer: "7 Years Old, 11 Years Old, 21 Years Old"
    },
    {
      question: "What years do the “Vegas” or Upper #3 Hooks DisAppear?",
      answer: "9 Years Old, 13 Years Old, 23 Years Old"
    },
    {
      question: "What composite is the hardest, brightest, whitest material of the tooth and necessary for chewing?",
      answer: "Enamel"
    },
    {
      question: "Do mares get Canines?",
      answer: "Yes but they are usually small and not dominate, dominate canines are usually found in male horses."
    },
    {
      question: "When does the bottom of the Enamel Cup turn circular and loose its ability to hold cementum on the Lower #2’s?",
      answer: "14 Years Old"
    },
    {
      question: "When does a Horse shed their very first Babytooth (Cap)?",
      answer: "2 1⁄2 Years Old"
    },
    {
      question: "What Composite is the body of the tooth?",
      answer: "Dentin"
    },
    {
      question: "What Composite protects enamel on the Inside of the Cup?",
      answer: "Cementum"
    },
    {
      question: "When is a horse considered “A Full Mouth Horse?”",
      answer: "5 Years Old"
    }   
  ]
}